Uh, the history is giving me the gash.
62, look at that.
Russian mess.
Shit, I haven't been cheating that much.
Mic working?
Cool.
What is this thing?
Okay, first thing I want to comment on is the weird blue streak in the bottom.
That's messed up.
It should show TE instead of TM in the upper right. That's also just something that I thought was done. It's not done
It's locking the player too. Now. It's just showing random blue and red stuff. It's really screwed up
When I hit up, yeah, it's still locking the player too, but whatever it's fine
What I wanted to do
Just not sure if that's what you wanted to do. Alright, here we go
Alright
Alright, I see some weird flickering which I think is, it's all buggy, a buggy disaster.